(Bernadette:)So, what are you
working on these days?
(Amy:)I'm studying
one-celled organisms
(Amy:)to try and find
the neurochemicals
(Amy:)that lead to the feeling
of shame.
(Bernadette:)What would a one-celled organism
have to be embarrassed about?
(Penny:)Same as all of us, getting out
of a car without underwear.
(Bermadette:)Speaking of underwear,
(Bermadette:)I have some interesting news...
(Penny:)Okay, if it's
sometimes Howie wears yours,
(Penny:)Leonard already told us.
(Bernadette:)He was being funny.
(Bernadette:)I'm pretty sure.
(Bernadette:)Anyway, I was asked to be
a part of a magazine article
(Bernadette:)about the 50 sexiest female
scientists in California.
(Bernadette:)Isn't that cool?
(Amy:)I think it's awful.
(Penny:)Why would you say that?
(Amy:)Bernadette is a
successful microbiologist.
(Amy:)She should be celebrated for
her achievements, not her looks.
(Amy:)I mean, what kind of message
does that send?
I think the message is-- "check
out the rack on that scientist."
(Bernadette:)Why can't someone be thought
of as both smart and pretty?
(Amy:)I just don't think
a professional woman should have